(まひろ)よっ と… ほっと…｡
(まひろ)うう… ﾄｲﾚ ﾄｲﾚ～｡
Gotta pee, gotta pee!
(かえで)おっ？
Huh?
すぅ…｡
ん～？
んっ！
(ﾄｲﾚの水が流れる音)
(かえで)ﾌﾌﾌｯ｡
見～た～な～！
ひぃい!?
You saw... didn't you?!
What's here is gone
What's gone is here
Today a cucumber, tomorrow a clam
Gotta check my trousers, trance, trance, trance
What's his is gone
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
What's hers is here
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
My pronouns are in shambles!
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Gone are the days of making wagies seethe
oyama Mahiro
(Bye-bye alright! I'm still unemployable!)
oyama Mihari
Without balls I just can't get up for it
(Scratch that, grow a pair! I won't stand for this!)
Ah, having peered into a queer new world
I've been bewitched by its siren song
I dove right in and the water's great
Cute outfits, makeup galore, and hairstyles aplenty
The world of women is calling my name
Wait, I'm a dude! Or am I?
(Are!)
(Who!)
Some part of my identity is crumbling
(It's me!)
Leading to a newborn sense of wonder
As an unknown sensation pervades my psyche
Awaken, my inner cute girl!
With proper stimulation comes a happy ending?
What's here is gone
What's gone is here
Today a cucumber, tomorrow a clam
Gotta check my trousers, trance, trance, trance
What's his is gone
What's hers is here
My manhood's in total shambles!
#f5f0ee Mahiro's Close Encounter
Perfect.
(みはり)あ…｡
うん！
What's going on?
Save me, Mihari!
んっ？
何してんの？
So, uh...
うぅ 助けてみはり～！
She and I were classmates back in middle school.
I'm Kaede. Nice to meetcha!
ﾌ ﾌﾌ～｡
ええと…｡
She seems a little colorful to be one of Mihari's friends.
こちら中学時代の同級生で…｡
Is she one of those gyaru fashionistas?
かえでだよ～ よろしくね～！
うぅ…｡
ﾌﾌｯ｡
Ugh, this is way outside my comfort zone as a home security officer!
If she were to find out who I really am...
《みはりの友達にしては
少しﾊﾃﾞな…｡
You creep! Pervert!
ｷﾞｬﾙってﾔﾂか？
ぐぅ！ 自宅警備員には
荷が重すぎる～｡
You shut-in cross-dressing weirdo!
Oh god, oh god, oh god, oh god...
もし正体が ﾊﾞﾚたりしたら…》
So what's your name?
のぞき魔！ 痴漢！
I-I-I'm, u-u-um...
変態女装 ｺﾞﾐﾆｰﾄ！
Mahiro.
ｱﾊﾞﾊﾞﾊﾞﾊﾞ！
お名前は～？
Aww, she's shy! What a cutie.
You never told me you had a little sister, Mihari.
Hang on.
ま まま ままま まひろ… です｡
Oh, well, you know? Family stuff.
ｱﾊｯ！ 照れちゃってかわいい～！
Mhmm, yup.
あれ けど みはりって妹いたっけ｡
えっ!?
うわ!?
Ah, gotcha, gotcha.
ああ～！ ちょ ちょっとﾜｹｱﾘで！
ふんふん！
Oh, that's right!
Sorry, Kaede. Would you mind keeping her company for a bit?
ふ～ん そっかそっか！
I still have a paper to finish up for college.
(まひろ/みはり)はあ～｡
ﾋｯﾋﾋ！
うわっ！
Huh?
Man, getting into college early sounds rough.
そうだ！ ごめんかえで
Sure thing! As a mere high schooler, I've got time to kill.
ちょっとその子と
遊んでてくれる？
大学のﾚﾎﾟｰﾄが少し残ってて…｡
はっ？
You're the best!
おっ 飛び級大学生は大変だ～｡
D-Don't leave me, Mihari!
ｵｯｹ ｵｯｹ～ 暇なJKに任せとき！
助かる～！
えっ？
(立ち去る足音)
So...
ま 待って みはり～！
What do you like to do in your free time, Mahiro-chan?
Uh! I like... reading manga and... p-playing games.
ねぇ まひろちゃんは
普段何して遊んでるの？
You play games?! So do I!
え… 漫画読んだり とか…
げ ｹﾞｰﾑとか…｡
See? It's that puzzle game everyone's playing.
ｹﾞｰﾑ！ ｱﾀｼもやってるよ～！
あ…｡
Oh... I don't play that one.
Oh, you don't?
ほら！ 人気のﾊﾟｽﾞﾙのやつ！
Never mind, then.
あ… それはやってない…｡
I give up.
Oh?
ああ！ ちがうか～ ｱﾊﾊﾊ｡
あ そっか そっか～｡
I guess it is about lunchtime, huh?
ぐ… もう無理…｡
Let's eat something, shall we?
おっ｡
ふぇ…｡
(おなかが鳴る音)
ｱｯﾊﾊﾊ！ そういやもうお昼じゃん｡
I'll just whip something up from leftovers.
一緒になんか食べよ～｡
んっ？
You're gonna cook?
I've actually got a little sister, too.
残り物で勝手に作っちゃおっか｡
So I cook for her all the time.
料理 するの？
I'm the domestic type, you know?
ｱﾀｼも妹いるんだよね～｡
Do you cook, Mahiro-chan?
よく作ってあげてんの｡
家庭的っしょ～？
I've never done it before.
It's pretty easy. Watch.
まひろちゃんは？ お料理｡
したことない…｡
簡単だよ～ 見ててごらん｡
～
んっ｡
All right, let's dig in!
Right.
いただきま～す｡
…ます｡
It's yummy!
Really? I'm so glad!
あ ん…｡
ん おいしい！
ﾎﾝﾄ？ よかった～！
It's weird, but...
this feels kinda nice.
ﾌﾌﾝ ん～！
あ～ん！
(かえで)ﾌﾌﾌ…｡
I'm so full.
《なんかこの感じ
ちょっとｱﾘ かも…》
Same.
Let's take the rest up to your sister later, okay?
(電車の音)
Okay.
お腹いっぱいだね～｡
うん～｡
I thought a gyaru would be more of a wild child.
お姉ちゃんには
あとで持っていってあげようね｡
うん…｡
So, Mahiro-chan...
You've never done it before, have you?
《ｷﾞｬﾙって もっとこう…
乱れてるｲﾒｰｼﾞだったけど…》
Wha?
Maybe I could give you a little demonstration.
まひろちゃんってさ～
まだシたことないでしょ？
ん？
Scratch that! She's frickin' crazy!
U-U-U-Uh! W-Wait! B-B-Back up!
ﾌﾌｯ お姉さんが教えてあげよっか｡
There's nothing to be embarrassed about.
《やっぱ 乱れまくりだ～！》
Leave it to me. I'll take care good of you.
は うわああ！ ちょ…｡
ちょちょ あ ちょっ！ 待って！
Now, close your eyes.
恥ずかしがることないんだよ…｡
B-But we...
Just try to relax.
私に任せて 大丈夫だから｡
My head's gonna kaboom!
ねっ？
あわ あわわぁ…｡
目を閉じて…｡
だ だめえぇ…｡
楽にして…｡
There! All done!
はわ…｡
ﾊﾟｰになるぅ～ ぐっ…｡
See? You're all dolled up!
よし 完成～！
～
She was talking about makeup?!
Mihari's not as into this stuff as I am, you know?
(かえで)ほ～ら かわいくなった！
Sorry to disappoint.
《ﾒｲｸの話か～！》
Even you had your bare-face era, Kaede.
みはりは
こういうの疎いからね～｡
疎くて悪かったわね～｡
(まひろ/かえで)あ…｡
Oh, no! Not that!
High school changed you, you traitor!
かえでだって… 昔はこ～んな！
Delete it!
Not a chance!
Oh, hang on!
うわあ！ やだ～！
I could show you how to coordinate an outfit, too!
高校ﾃﾞﾋﾞｭｰしよって～！
裏切り者～！
Can you take me up to your room?
Absolutely not!
あ 消して～！
ﾀﾞﾒﾀﾞﾒ～！
あ そうだ！
次はお洋服ｺｰﾃﾞもしてあげる！
All right, I should head home.
Bye-bye, Mahiro-chan.
ちょっとお部屋見せて～？
And thanks for having me, Mihari!
それはﾀﾞﾒ～！
(ｶﾗｽの鳴き声)
Kaede's great with people, don't you think?
(かえで)そんじゃ
そろそろ帰るね～｡
I thought she'd be good socialization practice for you.
ﾊﾞｲﾊﾞｲ～ まひろちゃん！
みはりも ありがとね～｡
You could've told me.
人あたりのいい子でしょ かえで｡
But you're right, she was pretty nice.
お兄ちゃんの人付き合いの
練習になるかな～って｡
お前なあ…｡
She's kinda like...
the perfect big sister!
ﾌｯ でもたしかによかったな
かえでちゃん…｡
You could learn a lot from her, you know?
あれは そう… お姉ちゃん！
Mihari-oneechan.
ﾌﾌ～ よ～く見習えよ｡
Huh?
ONIMAI
Onimai.
みはり｢お姉ちゃん｣！
The Greatest Hit of the Century
The greatest hit of the century!
えっ？
＜今世紀最大の話題作＞
Wait for me!
～
It feels like I've known you for years.
But then fate tore them apart.
(汽笛)
(ﾚｵﾅﾙﾄﾞ)待ってくれ！
I won't let you die here!
(ﾚｵﾅﾙﾄﾞ)君とは
初めて会った気がしないな｡
Leonardo!
＜ そして宿命のときがせまる＞
君は生き残るんだ！
(ｹｲﾄ)ﾚｵﾅﾙﾄﾞ！
Titanic in Space
Titanic in Space.
(ﾚｵﾅﾙﾄﾞ)は… ぐあ！
(ｹｲﾄ)きゃあ！
ﾚｵﾅﾙﾄﾞ～！
It's finally out!
I wonder when they'll start streaming it online.
＜ｽﾍﾟｰｽ ﾀｲﾀﾆｯｸ＞
Oh, wait! I wanna go see this one, too!
ようやく公開か～！
ﾈｯﾄ配信は いつごろかな～？
(扉が開く音)
It's a shame my duty as home security officer doesn't allow it.
(ｷｰﾎﾞｰﾄﾞとﾏｳｽの音)
Why don't we go see it together?
ああ これ｡
んっ？
私も見たいんだよね～｡
Wha?
ﾌﾝｯ 映画館に行けないのが
自宅警備員のつらいところだ｡
The Greatest Hit of the Century
なんなら一緒に行っちゃう？
へぇ？
～
Where even are we? Isn't this a mall?
There's a movie theater upstairs.
Ngh, the lively atmosphere! It burns my soul!
うぅ… なんだよここ…｡
You're so dramatic.{having read all kinds of LNs riffing on the concept of chuuniness, I really want to change this, but I'll resist. it works fine in english.}
ｼｮｯﾋﾟﾝｸﾞﾓｰﾙじゃないか！
Hey, guys! Sorry I'm late!
上が映画館なのよ｡
Kaede-chan!
It's nice to see you again, Mahiro-chan!
でぇおぉ…
陽気な波動が身体をむしばむ…｡
Same here!
中二病か｡
'Kay, how 'bout we do a little shopping?
やっほ～ おまたせ～！
かえでちゃん！
まひろちゃ～ん！
Huh?
P-Psst, what about the movie?
ひさしぶり～！
うん～！
Well, we kinda have some time to kill before it starts...
じゃ 軽くｱｸｾでも見て行く？
I've been tricked.
Hurray!
へっ？ お おい… 映画は？
Hm?
I get to go on a date with Mahiro-chan!
Wha? W-Wait a sec...
実は はじまるまで
かなり時間が～｡
ﾊﾒられた～｡
わ～い まひろちゃんとﾃﾞｰﾄだ～｡
あ ちょ ちょっと～！
ﾌﾌｯ｡
～
This hair clip would look great on you, Mihari.
It's okay. I don't need one.
You sure?
みはり これなんか似合いそう！
Ugh, I'm exhausted.
う～ん 髪留めはいいかな～｡
Going shopping for girl stuff really takes it out of you.
(かえで)そう？
Yeah, great choices!
ひぇ～ この疲労感…｡
Oh, shoot! I completely forgot!
女の子の買い物はﾊｰﾄﾞすぎる
んっ？
Huh?
We gotta check out the bathing suits!
ああ いいね～！
We're not done yet?!
んっ ああ！ 忘れてた～！
んっ？
(かえで)水着も見ないと！
まだ見るの～!?
(ざわめき)
Ta-da!
What d'ya think?
Whoa...
Y-You're stacked...
Oh, don't make me blush!
じゃあ～ん どうどう？
You too, Mihari! Let's see you!
ひょええぇ～｡
お おっきいね…｡
I haven't worn a swimsuit since gym class back in middle school.
やだも～ みはりも出てきなよ～！
はは～｡
H-How do I look?
うぅ… 水着着るの
中学の授業以来かも…｡
You look amazing!
It really suits her! Right?
Yeah, well, you know?
It was a tough act to follow.
ど どうかな？
That reminds me.
いいじゃん！
よく似合ってるよ ねぇ？
Didn't you say you wanted a swimsuit too, Mahiro-chan?
まあ あれだ｡ 相手が悪かった…｡
Go and pick one to try on!
Let's go!
んん… そういえば
まひろちゃんも
水着欲しがってたよね～？
Gosh, it's perfect!
選んでもらいなよ～｡
ｵｯｹ～！
え ええぇ…｡
You look adorable!
I can't go out in public wearing this!
It's basically underwear, for crying out loud!
やだ 似合う～！
(かえで)かわいいよ～！
Then how about this?
You could also cover up with a beach wrap, if you'd like.
こんな格好で人前に出れるか！
Nnngh...
下着と大差ないじゃんか！
じゃあ こんなのは？
Why don't you try on a one-piece instead?
(かえで)ﾊﾟﾚｵを
巻くのもありだよ～｡
Yeah, I feel more comfortable in this.
うぬぬ…｡
普通のﾜﾝﾋﾟｰｽも着てみたら～？
Then it's settled!
あ…｡ ん～ これならまぁ…｡
Why did I even buy this?
I kinda bought one on impulse...
(かえで/みはり)決まり～！
Hang on. I feel like we're forgetting something...
The movie!
買ってどうする…｡
私もつい…｡
あれ 何か忘れてる気が…｡
あっ 映画～！
They have returned!
(ざわめき)
The long-awaited next entry in the worldwide hit series,
"Clone Wars 7: The Battle Within."
(走る息遣い)
We made it!
This version of me just doesn't know when to quit.
The AC's a bit strong in here, huh?
＜ﾔﾂらが帰ってきた｡
全世界待望のｼﾘｰｽﾞ最新作
｢ﾊﾞﾄﾙ ｵﾌﾞ ｸﾛｰﾝｽﾞ 俺大戦ｾﾌﾞﾝ｣＞
Look, it's about to start.
間に合った～｡
I won't let you die here!
ちょっとｸｰﾗｰ強いね｡
Leonardo!
ほら はじまるよ！
(開演ﾌﾞｻﾞｰ)
おお～！
君は生き残るんだ！
ﾚｵﾅﾙﾄﾞ！
Nngh, I really need to go!
(ﾚｵﾅﾙﾄﾞ)はぁ ぐああ！
(映画の爆発音)
And right at the best part, too.
I'm gonna go to the bathroom.
ん んん ぐ…｡
Okay.
うぅう… もう限界…｡
うぅ こんないいところで…｡
I'm a bit nervous about using the girls' bathroom.
ちょっとﾄｲﾚ…｡
は～い｡
Wha?
(走る息遣い)
What... the hell?
気が引けるなあ 女子ﾄｲﾚ…｡
I was sobbing!
Titanic in Space
あ…｡
Me too!
Titanic in Space
Why is it only the girls' bathroom?!
That last scene had me bawling.
なん だと？
Titanic in Space
My eyes kinda hurt from crying so much!
泣けたよね～｡
ﾏｼﾞ泣けた～｡
うぅ どうして女子ﾄｲﾚだけ…｡
I-I can't hold it much longer!
おうぉお…｡
Leonardo!
こ… ほお おお…｡
も もう 無理ぃ～｡
Mahiro-chan? Are you in here?
(ｹｲﾄ)ﾚｵﾅﾙﾄﾞ～！
Oh, dear. So you didn't make it, huh?
まひろちゃ～ん いる～？
(ﾉｯｸ)
Don't worry. It's okay.
(すすり泣き)
Looks like you didn't get any on your skirt.
ああ～ 失敗しちゃったか～｡
I'll go buy you a change of underwear, okay?
Do you think you can wait for me here?
う ううぅ…｡
うんうん 大丈夫｡
Yeah...
Don't worry, I won't tell Mihari.
ｽｶｰﾄは濡れてないし
今 替えの下着を買ってくるね｡
ここで待てる？
うん…｡
みはりには内緒だよ｡
あ…｡
は くしゅん…｡
What took you guys so long?
んっ？
The line was pretty long.
ﾄｲﾚ長くない？
はぇ…｡
Onee-chan...
混んでてさ～｡
は…｡
～
ONIMAI
Onimai.
お姉ちゃん…｡
ONIMAI
Lunch sure is taking a while.
Mihari better not be sleeping in.
んっ｡
(おなかが鳴る音)
Jeez...
昼めしおっそいな～｡
Really not living up to the "Onee-chan" title now, are we?
みはりのﾔﾂ まだ寝てるのか～？
Hey, "Onee-chan"! What happened to lunch?
まったく…
｢お姉ちゃん｣の風上にもおけん！
おい｢お姉ちゃん｣ ご飯まだ～？
はぁ…｡
んっ？ ん～｡
Oh, you're on your period. I've been there.
I've got a cold, silly!
はぁ… んん…｡
Oh, no! My bad!
I'm fine.
ああ～ 生理… わかる～｡
I took some medicine, so I just need some rest.
風邪よ！ あ…｡
You'll have to make do with instant ramen for lunch.
うわああ！ ごめん…｡
There's some in the cupboard—
平気… 薬も飲んだし
寝てれば治る…｡
Mihari...
Soy Sauce
お昼はｶｯﾌﾟめんで我慢して…｡
Mihari's always staying up late writing reports.
戸棚にあるから ｺﾞﾎｺﾞﾎｯ…｡
And she does all the housework, too!
みはり…｡
Ugh, what am I doing calling her "Onee-chan"?!
(風鈴の音)
She's your little sister, dammit!
ｱｲﾂ ここんとこ
ﾚﾎﾟｰﾄで徹夜したりして…
I can do this! For her!
そのうえ家事まで…｡
むぅ… 何が｢お姉ちゃん｣だ！
Besides, housework can't be that bad!
It's my duty as home security officer!
みはりは お前の｢妹｣だろ!?
I'll do a bang-up job and show her what a great big brother I can be!
やるぞ… やってやる！
家事ぐらい楽勝だ！
Oops...
これもいわば自宅警備！
They're a little soggy.
華麗にこなして
兄の偉大さを知らしめる！
あ…｡
ふぅ… すぅ～！
Bleach or fabric softener? Non-alkaline or alkaline?
ちょっと のびてる…｡
Who cares? It's all the same, right?
んん… ふっ！ いっ！
漂白剤 柔軟剤 中性 ｱﾙｶﾘ…｡
Anybody can use a vacuum!
Oh, yeah. I should make Mihari something to eat.
まあ だいたい一緒だろ！
さすがに
掃除機くらいは使えるぞ～！
In times like this, nothing beats some homemade rice porridge!
あ そういや みはりの食事…｡
Rice porridge, huh?
うわあ！
(掃除機の異音)
Mahiro-chan
Incoming Call
やっぱこういうときは
おかゆだよな！
Mahiro-chan
Incoming Call
Mahiro-chan?
おかゆ～｡
Hm? What's up?
How to make rice porridge?
It's really simple, actually!
But wait, does that mean Mihari's under the weather?
まひろちゃ～ん？
Is she okay? Should I come over and help?
んっ？ どうしたの？
Oh, no, it's okay.
(かえで)おかゆの作り方？
めちゃくちゃ簡単だよ～！
I think I've got this. But thanks!
てかなに
みはり寝込んじゃってるの!?
大丈夫？ 応援行こっか？
あ…｡
あ ううん！ 今日は大丈夫！
ありがとう！
～
Easy now...
ふぅ…｡
んん～ おわ!? うぅ…｡
Now I put it on low heat and let it simmer, right?
そ～っと…｡
弱火にして あとは煮込むだけ…｡
(ｾﾐの声)
Mihari
Hup.
(寝息)
I made you rice porridge.
ん…｡
(扉を開ける音)
What? You did?
よっ…｡
I can't promise it's any good, though.
おかゆ作ったぞ～｡
え… お兄ちゃんが？
味は保証しないからな｡
H-Hey! What happened?! What's wrong?!
I just... I can't believe...
Onii-chan, you cooked for me!
わあ… うっ…｡
んっ？
うえぇ～ん！
うぇ!?
All right, already! Just eat it while it's hot, okay?
お おい！ なんだよ なんで!?
だって…
お兄ちゃんがごは… ごはん～！
Okay.
ああ… わかったから
いいから 食べろ！
It's so bland, but I'm so happy!
I forgot to add salt.
はむ… くぅ…｡
味がないよ～！ でもうれしい～！
Change clothes before you go back to sleep, okay?
Okay.
塩 入れ忘れた…｡
(ｾﾐの声)
寝る前に着替えろよ｡
うん…｡
(扉の開閉音)
はあ…｡
Morning, Mihari-chan!
Morning, Kaede!
Hey, what's with the hair clip?
かえで:おはよ～
みはりちゃん！
Oh, this?
おはよ～ かえで！
My big brother gave it to me.
(かえで)あれ
どうしたのその髪留め｡
He said it was a reward for doing so well on that test.
Aww, must be nice to have such a sweet older brother.
ああ これね｡
ｴﾍﾍ… お兄ちゃんがくれたんだ！
Do you have any siblings, Kaede?
I have a little sister, actually.
こないだのﾃｽﾄのご褒美にって！
But honestly, we don't have much in common.
優しいお兄ちゃんだね いいな～！
Aw, that's too bad.
かえでは兄弟いないの？
But she's super cute all the same.
妹がいるよ～｡
I like baking cookies and stuff for her when I can.
でも趣味がね～ 合わないみたい｡
Wait, you know how to bake?
そうなんだ～｡
Teach me, teach me!
でも ま やっぱりかわいいよ！
Of course!
We can bake at my place together sometime!
たまにお菓子とか
ｸｯｷｰ作ってあげたり！
Hurray!
えぇ かえで お料理できるの？
教えて教えて！
いいよ～ 今度うちで一緒に作ろ！
やった～！
(鳥のさえずり)
んん… ん～！ はぁ…｡
あ…｡
Onii-chan...
(寝息)
うぅ…｡
Thank you.
お兄ちゃん…｡
Perfect!
Mihari
ありがとう｡
よし！
～
My big brother was always so sweet to me.
んっ？
But as time went by, he gradually stopped spending time with me.
ﾌﾌｯ｡
＜昔は優しかったお兄ちゃん｡
I worked so hard at school and sports because I craved his praise so badly.
それがいつからか
だんだん遊んでくれなくなって＞
(ｵｰﾌﾞﾝの音)
Something smells nice in here.
＜ お兄ちゃんに褒められたくて
勉強もｽﾎﾟｰﾂも
がんばったんだけどな…＞
A-Are you sure it's okay for you to be up?
Yup, I'm all better now!
ふああ～
なんか甘いにおいがするな…｡
Look, I baked cookies.
えっ もう起きて大丈夫なのか？
Sho good!
うん もう大丈夫｡
You've always been so good at baking, Mihari!
ほら ｸｯｷｰ焼いたよ！
Actually, this is a recipe Kaede taught me a while back.
は～ はんっ！
Oh, really? Wow!
んま～！ やっぱり
みはりは料理うまいよな～！
But we've gotten to talk a lot more recently.
No wonder it tastes so good!
これね
昔 かえでに教わったﾚｼﾋﾟだよ！
In a way... it's just like old times.
かえでちゃんに？ へぇ～！
There's plenty more, okay?
Woo-hoo!
They're so good, I could eat them all day!
＜最近はだんだん会話も増えて
なんだかちょっと
昔に戻ったみたい＞
Our roles are a little reversed, but...
おかわりもあるからね｡
I'd love it if we could stay like this just a little while longer.
おほ～！
これならいくらでも食えそうだ！
ﾌﾌｯ…｡
＜兄妹の立場は逆だけど
With a one-two-three, it's time to play
できるなら…
もうしばらくこのまま…＞
Come and join us in a secret hideaway
Hey, br- I mean, Mahiro! Wanna try on a maid outfit?
Huh?
No, it's gotta be a bunny-girl costume!
H-Hold on!
Let's go with a dress, we can even match!
Point is, it's time to strip!
Hey! Cut it out!
Noooooooooo!
A genius has at a docile lab rat
(And in the night...)
A single dose, perfection isn't slow!
(Hey, what the heck?)
Cutie acquired, cuddles required
Partner recaptured, hey, let's go!
(Oh, deary me!)
(Time for a show)
Let's have a sleepover, yay, yay, yay!
(And someone's gonna feel like they're the odd one out!)
The girls got a little somethin' goin' on tonight
(Send help, I don't know how to feel)
With a one-two-three, it's time to play
And break the gender barrier
Soon enough your heart's athrob
Time to welcome you into a place you've never known!
(One! Two!)
(It's a bouncy world!)
It's time to reassess! No more stress!
Just submit, surrender, don't obsess!
Girls with itty-bitty bodies can still
Be packed with secrets deep within!
Give your all, have a ball!
Right until the cards'll start to fall!
There's one thing that you really should know:
Girl power makes the world go 'round!
If there's an identity crisis coming on, it can wait another day
I take it all back!
Onii-chan?!
Illustration: Kay Yu
Next Episode: Mahiro's New Friend
前言撤回～！
See you next time!
お兄ちゃん～？